FROM ME TO YOU
FIRST SNOW
It was such a relief the following day...
'cause Chizu came to school with a
refreshed look on her face as if the
burden of her heartache had finally been
lifted. She still isn't going out of
her way to chat with Sanada... but she also
doesn't seem to be completely
ignoring him like yesterday.
I've been thinking, let's
have some fun! For real!
Like what?
Long as it's not
all-you-can-eat something, I'm down.
- But why not?
- I'll get fat!
Ah! ...
Spending time with Chizu today, she
seems to be back to her usual self.
I sang my lungs out! I haven't gone to
karaoke since the field day after-party!
And ya know what? I think I'm a
little less pissed at Ryu now, too.
I'm so glad!
So do you guys wanna go and
get some ramen on the way home?
You mean at Sanada's place?
Ya sure?
On second thought, seeing his
face might piss me off again.
That's probably true.
I know we've been talking a lot of trash
about Ryu as of late, but if I'm being
honest, I can't help but be kinda glad
that he was there. -If Ryu hadn't let you
vent at him, you may not have been able
to let it all out like that, Chizu. -Yeah.
There's something I figured out after
that. That I... want to try having a proper
conversation with Toru one more time.
I didn't even realize that
until I fought with Ryu.
Not that it matters, now that I know it
would've been impossible for me to do that
- before.
- So, what do you plan
- to say to him next time?
-"I love you."
Like, can you imagine if I said that
for real? Don't tell me you took that
- seriously?
- S- Sorry, but that's not funny.
So that was meant to be a joke...
Nah, why would I? I already
know what Toru's reply would be.
Wait, is that...?
What's up?
What?
Chii.
Sorry, I need to borrow her real quick.
To... huh? But... how come?!
What do ya mean? To see you, Chii.
This way.
You're in a miniskirt...
Just like you wanted...
You're right!
Please... Please let Chizu be able to
tell him everything that's in her heart
The next time I see her, no matter what
happens, please let her heart be at peace.
- Wanna grab tea somewhere?
- Sure.
- When'd you get here?
- Just now.
You staying overnight?
Nah, I'll be heading back later.
And work?
I worked extra hard today. I finished
everything up early so I could come here.
Do you have work tomorrow morning too?
It's just you'll be home so late.
Don't worry about boring stuff like that!
No... I'm happy.
I really am.
Um... So, by the way...
- That was a total three sixty!
- H-Hey! I'm wearing a miniskirt!
That's right. You've always
had your legs showing, huh Chii?
Yay!
Looks like you're still as tough as ever!
I'm kinda an old man, so I'd freeze like
- that.
- Crap! H-He's too used to seeing them.
- Y-You are not an old man!
- From the perspective of someone
your age, isn't 24 getting up there?
I dunno.
H- He's treating me
even more like a kid now.
And when I have such killer legs too.
This sucks...
Seriously. My poor thighs.
Hey. Where'd you park
your car by the way?
I left it back at home.
- Why?
- 'Cause back in the day when we hung out,
I never drove a car. We'd go wherever on
foot.
I thought we'd walk together
for old times' sake, Chii.
Hold on one second.
Welcome!
CHEF'S BREAD FAIR
Here. Pork bun.
Also... this one. Red bean.
We used to eat these all the time.
Yeah.
Pork bun, red bean bun, pork, or red bean.
- Which one do you like most?
- Well, once I eat something
sweet, I want something salty after.
But if I buy two, that's my whole
allowance. Also, if I eat two and can't
finish dinner, my mom
is gonna kick my butt!
Aw man! I want both of them.
Oh, now that's a problem...
Pork bun, red bean. Pork
bun, red bean. Pork bun...
One pork and one red bean bun please.
Here. Let's share half of each.
And don't tell Ryu, ya got it?
That not enough? Guess you could easily
eat two whole ones by yourself now, huh?
Nah, I prefer this.
Hey look! See it? That streetlight there!
When I was in high school, on my way
back from hanging with friends at night... I
always used to take this street home And
when I did, I'd often see a kid near that
exact light.
I wondered why the heck there was a
little kid out and about that late. But
- when I looked closer--
- Why're you telling me a
- ghost story all of a sudden?
- It was you, Chii!
You were out catching stag beetles and
at three o'clock in the morning! Man, you
sure freaked me out that time!
Y-Yeah. Guess I did. I remember when
I was a kid, I'd wake up super early.
And then, the two of us
would always walk home together.
While we looked up at the stars and stuff.
Toru!
Hm?
What's that star called?
Hmm, I dunno... The Big Star!
Big Star!
Honestly, the only
constellation I know is Orion.
Orion?
Yeah.
Where's that?
Yeah, where's Orion?
I don't see it. There's supposed
to be a trio of stars lined up.
Where's the trio?
So, it was a winter
constellation apparently.
The sky's so dark out
here in the countryside.
You remember all that.
Yeah, of course I do.
I wonder if Chizu got to say
everything she needed to say this time.
It's kind of crazy... how
many things seem to happen...
When you really like someone.
There are times when it's
tough when you even want to cry.
But there can be a whole lot of
happiness mixed in there too.
Yes.
I remember a lot... like
when you tripped over there.
And when you were buying
food with Ryu over there too.
Toru was always smiling at me.
Chii!
I walked down this street so
many times with you and Ryu.
And now, this is Ryu's jogging route.
Look, it's that grass field.
- That was where Ryu made you start crying.
- I can't believe you remember that...
How about now though?
Does he still make you cry?
Uh, no, of course not!
Ryu, you idiot! He pisses me off so much!
Uh no, he doesn't do
that! Seriously! Not at all!
Yeah?
It's just! I get pissed at him. It's like
an automatic response to take my anger out
on him...
Well, Ryu's a very kind person.
And he never tells a single lie either.
You and Ryu are super close, and because
of that, the things he says can get under
your skin way more easily. You might not
get as pissed if it were someone else's
words.
I see. So those are the kinds of
fights the two of you get into these days.
And that uniform. It suits you Chii.
It really made me think, "Wow,
she's a high schooler already.
Toru...
I assumed you'd never get married... that
you'd never be able to settle down with
- anyone.
- Well that makes me sound pretty awful!
What happened to make
you decide to get married?
You're only 24.
I couldn't help but feel I wanted to
stay with this girl for the rest of my
- life.
- I get it. Ever since I was
little, that's how I've felt about you.
Your girl... she seems like she's
a really gentle and sweet person.
I get that, she may not look it
but she's actually super strong.
I knew it.
No matter how much you care about me, or
how many memories we share even if I'm in
high school now, a neighborhood
kid is just a neighborhood kid.
Oh?
Chii. Alright it's your turn to say it.
Just do it.
Do you know why I always
call you "Chii" as a nickname?
No clue.
Sound it out.
Chii...
Enunciate!
Chii.
That's it.
There's a smile!
- Toru!
- Chii!
Chii! Chii.
Toru... I like you.
And I like you too.
I knew you'd say that.
That's not the way I meant it though.
But... I'm happy.
I was... wondering...
I'm not your real little sister, just a
kid from the neighborhood. but the next
time you're here to visit, I was
wondering... can I still come and see you?
Don't be dumb. Stop
acting like a stranger!
To me, you are my little sister. And you
might be cuter than Ryu. But don't tell
him that, okay?
Little sister, huh?
I'll bet when he's with his fiancé, he
shows her all the different sides he has...
But I'm still happy.
I can tell... that you've
always cared about me...
Even if it's as a big brother.
Chii!
Toru! Congrats, kay?
Oh, you went out for a jog?
- Where's Chizuru?
- Home. I walked her there
- myself so no need to worry.
- Heading back?
Yep. I'll visit again soon.
Wait here for a second.
Here, the bread.
You're a reliable guy
Ryu. When are they from?
Oh... yesterday... wait.
- Should be okay though. It's winter.
- Thank you.
Whoa! You've gotten big too, haven't
you! I bet you're gonna be taller than me.
Yep, I will, I'm
still in my growth spurt.
You and Chii are a lot alike
Not at all the flexible type.
Good luck. You're a much better
match for her than I would be.
Bro...
Bro?!
I was thinking the exact same thing.
He's a man all right.
Oh, Hi, Ryu, Chizu wasn't out with you?
No.
She's so late. I thought she'd be at your
place like usual. Goodness. what is that
child of mine up to now?
I think I might know
where she is. I'll go check.
Oh, thank you for that, honey.
Doesn't act it but even so,
she is still a girl, ya know...
Do you want me to comfort you?
Are you... trying to be sensitive
about my feelings? Or pick a fight?
Neither of those things.
What the heck?! What are
you doing out here then?
Because back when my brother was still
living at the house. this was the last
place he went to hang out. And it's also
where you were that day when he left here.
Didn't I tell you that I didn't want
you to talk to me for a little while?
Fine. I won't talk then.
I didn't mean it. Sorry.
And that one day was
your birthday too. Sorry.
Especially since the only one who
could've properly celebrated it with you
this year... was me. I'm sorry.
Nah, I mean, I don't think anyone
remembered... well, except for you, I guess.
Thank you for the bag.
It was you, huh? That called Toru.
'Cause when I asked Toru if he was
hungry, he said, "Ryu's giving me some
bread." Well, it's not
like I'm shocked or anything.
Even though you asked him to, it doesn't
change the fact he drove three and a half
hours to come here. It
made me happy. So, thank you.
It's exactly like you said before.
You knew I always liked Toru
even though I didn't stand a chance...
I guess, I never actually believed
that he could feel the same about me.
Maybe the entire time, I just looked
up to Toru as more of a big brother.
That's not it.
'Cause you really did love
him. And I always knew that.
Please comfort me, Ryu...
On that day... we had our
first snowfall of the year.
The holy night.
A silently growing desire.
Next time: "Christmas"